RALPH CADELIÑA

DEVELOPER

WEBSITE: ralphcadelinaportfolio.vercel.app

CAREER **OBJECTIVE**

With a bachelor's degree holder in Information Technology with experience in the IT Industry particularly in Web Development. I venture in securing a position in a company where I can apply my experience that would best fit my qualifications. I aim to further enhance my values toward any responsibility that I will undertake.

SOFTWARE **DEVELOPMENT SKILLS**

- · HTML5, CSS, BOOTSTRAP
- · JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS
- . MATERIAL UI, CHAKRA UI
- · NODE JS
- FIREBASE
- API INTEGRATION (REST API)
- PHP, LARAVEL

SERVER ADMINISTRATION SKILLS

- SERVERS (WINDOWS SERVER 2008/2012)
- MICROSOFT OFFICE (365, WORD, EXCEL, POWERPOINT, ACCESS & OUTLOOK)
- DATABASE MANAGEMENT (MYSQL)
- COMPUTER HARDWARE & SOFTWARE (INSTALL, REPAIR, TROUBLESHOOT, SALES & MAINTENANCE)

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Surigao Education Center | 2012 - 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

JR. FRONTEND **DEVELOPER** KRE8TIB I.T. SERVICES | AUG 2022 - OCT 2022

• Build and implements static web pages and email templates

SITE

SURIGAO EDUCATION CENTER | ADMINISTRATOR NOV. 2021 - MAY 2022

- Manage the official domain of the institution.
- Build the website from template through wordpress.
- Arrange the content and information of the institution.

+639705368194